yappy.im 2017-12-07

# Yappy - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy   
Effective Date: October 27, 2016 

This Privacy Policy covers the Yappy Application, Services, and Website, which are owned and operated by MariusSoft LLC (“MariusSoft”). The terms “Application,” “Services,” and “Website” are defined in the Terms of Service at [www.yappy.im/businessTOS](http://www.yappy.im/businessTOS). 

MariusSoft is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and wishes to maintain a safe and secure environment for all users of the Application, Services, and Website. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information is treated. From time to time, MariusSoft may offer new services that may require MariusSoft to update this Privacy Policy. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact MariusSoft’s Privacy Administrator by email at [info@yappy.im](mailto:info@yappy.im). 

This Privacy Policy addresses the following issues regarding your privacy protection: 

INFORMATION COLLECTED BY MARIUSSOFT 

MariusSoft collects personal information from users for different purposes. Information gathered can be identified as either anonymous or identifiable. Anonymous information is information that cannot be traced back to the individual. Identifiable information is information that is specific to an individual. 

Automatically Collected Data / Log Data

Like most companies offering online services, the Application, Services, and Website gather certain information automatically from your computer or mobile device and store it. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, operating system, device type, browser type, content viewed, Internet services provider (ISP), location information, referring/exit pages, date/time stamps, and clickstream data. MariusSoft uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, administer the Application and Website, gather demographic information about its user base as a whole, and improve its level of service to you. 

Information You Provide

To use the Application and Services, a user must register for an account. A user may register by creating an account through the Application or Website. In either case, MariusSoft will collect the following information: (i) name, (ii) email address, and (iii) password. Alternatively, MariusSoft may allow a user to register using third party services (such as Google or Facebook) to authenticate the user’s identity. If a user registers using a third party service, you will be asked permission to share certain information from your third party account with MariusSoft. In addition, users must provide financial information in order to use the MariusSoft service. However, all financial information is processed through third-party payment processors, and MariusSoft does not collect or store a user’s financial information. The provision of this personally identifiable information is mandatory and if you choose not to submit the requested information we will not be able to provide you with an account. 

Service Data Provided by MariusSoft’s Customers

MariusSoft collects and stores information that is created, inputted, submitted, posted, transmitted, or stored by you or an individual authorized to use the Services through your account (“Agent”). This information (“Service Data”) may include electronic data, texts, messages, communications, phone numbers, Facebook account information, IP addresses, clickstream date, cookies, and other custom data provided by you to MariusSoft. 

If your personal information is collected and/or used by MariusSoft’s customers, you should review the privacy policies of such customers to understand how your personal information is collected and used. 

COOKIES 

MariusSoft uses cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s device to help us improve your access to and use of the Application, Services, or Website and identify repeat visitors. 

You can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of the Services. 

USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION 

Personally identifiable information collected is used primarily for the purpose it is collected (e.g., creating a user account). MariusSoft also may use a user’s email address as follows, provided that the user grants his/her consent to such additional use: 

• in internal surveys to obtain feedback on aspects of MariusSoft’s business; 

• to notify users of information MariusSoft thinks may be of interest to them; • to send communications or promotional materials; and 

• to provide, operate, maintain, analyze, improve and promote the Services. 

MariusSoft may also use personally identifiable information collected to contact users in connection with the inappropriate use of the Application, Services, or Website. 

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION 

From time to time, MariusSoft may disclose your personal information to organizations that perform services for or on behalf of MariusSoft, for example to provide customer service, for research, data processing, and to measure the use of our Application, Services, or Website. MariusSoft will share with these companies only that personal information that they need to work on our behalf. Some of these service providers may be located in other countries. Your personal information will be provided to these organizations only if they agree to use such information solely for the purpose of providing services to MariusSoft, and under the instructions of MariusSoft, and with respect to that information, to act in a manner consistent with the relevant principles articulated in this Privacy Policy. 

INFORMATION SECURITY 

The Application, Security, and Website have commercially reasonable security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about MariusSoft’s ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, or alteration to you or to any third party. Please review MariusSoft’s Terms of Service regarding MariusSoft’s liability for any loss, misuse, or alteration of personally identifiable information. 

UPDATING INFORMATION 

You have the right to correct and update the personal information collected about you through the Application, Services, or Website. You can make changes to your personal information at any time by logging into your account. You will need your email address and password in order to access your account. Alternatively, you may contact MariusSoft at [info@yappy.im](mailto:info@yappy.im). 

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

MariusSoft reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change in our information collection and handling practices, MariusSoft will notify by email those users who have provided an email address. Any changes will apply prospectively only. 

OPTING OUT OF RECEIVING EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS 

MariusSoft provides you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you register for an account but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference during the account creation process. If you opted-in to receive marketing communications but no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication. 

LINKS 

The Application, Services, or Website may contain links to third party applications, services, or websites. Please be aware that MariusSoft is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other applications, services, or websites. MariusSoft encourages users to read the privacy policies of any third party that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by MariusSoft. 

NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN 

The Application, Services, and Website is general audience app and does not direct any of its content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account. 

NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS 

MariusSoft does not disclose your information to third parties for marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive (a) information identifying all third-party companies to which we may have disclosed, within the past year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for those companies’ direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information, please email [info@yappy.im](mailto:info@yappy.im). 

CALIFORNIA DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE 

MariusSoft does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals. However, some third parties do track of your browsing activities. If you are visiting third party websites, your browser should allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties know you do not want to be tracked. 

INTERNATIONAL USERS 

MariusSoft is a U.S. company and the Application, Services, and Website are hosted in the United States. If you access the Application, Services, or Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region, country, or jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States privacy laws, please note that, by your use of the Application, Services, and Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. In addition, you understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where privacy laws may be less stringent than in your country. If you reside in a country or jurisdiction that provides access rights under law, you may access, correct or update the personal information through your account or by contacting MariusSoft at [info@yappy.im](mailto:info@yappy.im). 

U.S.-EUROPEAN UNION AND U.S.-SWITZERLAND SAFE HARBOR 

MariusSoft complies with the U.S.-European Union Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Switzerland Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit <https://build.export.gov/main/safeharbor/index.asp>. 

HOW TO CONTACT MARIUSSOFT ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS 

If you have any further questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [info@yappy.im](mailto:info@yappy.im). 

REQUIRED DISCLOSURES 

MariusSoft may disclose personal information when required by law or when MariusSoft believes in good faith that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our site.
